stacey.fatunbi@gmail.com • linkedin/in/stacey-onayiga • Washington, DC • 763.412.9000

Senior Scientific Technical Writer -

Meticulous and collaborative senior technical writer experienced in developing high quality technical content to clearly and efficiently explain highly complex data, systems, processes and products in deadline-driven healthcare, biotechnology, and medical device industries. Recognized for understanding and translating complicated information for target audiences, content creation, attention to detail, project management, and strong communication skills.

Technical Expertise:

Oxygen XML Editor DITA Microsoft Office Suite Adobe Creative Suite Jira HTML/CSS UX Design Certification (inprogress) Dreamweaver
Agile project development
Vasont
Notepad++
GitBash
Sourcetree

Python
Epic Medical Records System
Madcap Flare
SharePoint
FrameMaker
InDesign
Illustrator

May 2023-Present

Career Experience

Document Control Lead, QA QCS Technical Writer

ICON Strategic Solutions, Boston, MA

As a lead technical writer within R&D Quality consulted and su

As a lead technical writer within R&D Quality, consulted and supported Takeda Pharmaceuticals in high priority projects to streamline and simplify information architecture across research and development (R&D) group.

- Partnered with document, content, and/or process owners to provide controlled document authorship (SOPs, TOOLs, FORMs) within the R&D organization.
- Designed and curated project timelines, milestones, and writing activities for processes scoped for documentation redesign.
- Supported stakeholders and PMO in the redesign and development of information architecture which included, but was not limited to, scheduling, planning, and generation of quality documentation that adhered to organizational processes and standards.
- Lead the design and curation of a research and development writing style guide for R&D Quality group.
- Collaborated with team members, subject matter experts, and reviewers to meet deadlines and produce high quality work products in accordance with stakeholder requirements.

Page 2

- Lead and facilitated meetings with technical writing group to improve internal processes and develop ways to generate consistent documentation that adhered to style guide and organizational branding/requirements.
- Provided overall level of consistency to controlled documents within R&D quality.
- Drove clear, concise and consistent/harmonized controlled documents.
- Improved document quality through clear, concise written communication which included implementation of consistent corporate branding across documentation.
- Assisted with document management system (DMS workflow) requirements.
- Ensured consistency in metadata in document management system (DMS) for all documents to support proper mapping of information architecture.
- Adhered to established regulatory standards and organizational templates.
- Subject matter expert for good documentation practices and overall technical writing requirements and guidelines.

Technical Writer, Amazon Pharmacy, Arlington, VA March 2022 – March 2023 Supported and refined the information management system for Pillpack related documentation used across Amazon Pharmacy fulfillment sites nation-wide.

- Overhauled and standardized documentation for internal processes used on the Pillpack fulfillment floor.
- Successfully converted majority of SJIs to xml metalanguage in Q₃ through Q₄, reaching an approximate 70% completion rate of all Pillpack SJIs. This achievement allowed for single sourcing of information and better content reuse to promote consistency within documented processes.
- Streamline internal packaging and fulfillment process by vetting existing process paths in conjunction with associated documentation to reduce medical related errors/events (MREs) and other issues as it relates to packaging and fulfillment of medications for Amazon Pharmacy patients.
- Generated a standard SLA to create procedural documents (SJIs) for Pillpack fulfillment that built trust with stakeholders in regard to creating and delivering on documentation related requests in a timely manner, adhering to scope and projected deadlines.
- Partnered with stakeholders throughout Amazon Pharmacy Services to support initiatives to elevate, standardize, and host Amazon Pharmacy documentation across Rx Billing, Rx Billing, and Rx Acquisition.
- Engaged software development engineers (SDEs) within Amazon Pharmacy tech teams to bar raise and formalize API documentation.

Page | 3

- Self-taught on fundamentals of good API documentation through personalized research and collaboration with SDEs to identify pain points of current API content and how APIs could be better utilized by the customer.
- Mentored writing colleagues on the basics of good API documentation and how to successfully write for APIs.

Medical/Clinical Technical Writer

November 2020 - March 2022

Amazon Laboratories, Arlington, VA

Generated and formalized procedural documentation for scientists and laboratory technicians to safely conduct SAR-COV- $_2$ in-house test results using Saliva DirectTM test methods.

- Collaborated with key stakeholders to globalize and standardize clinical processes, where feasible, across laboratory sites nation-wide.
- Bar-raised and refined quality policy guidelines to outline good documentation practices as it relates to creating, formatting, revising and version control of laboratory documents.
- Implemented strategies to ensure protocols and procedures maintained a level of quality and version control as it went through the documentation lifecycle process.
- Joined forces with other writer colleagues to develop a unique information architecture system to manage clinical documentation and testing protocols utilized by laboratory personnel.
- Drove efforts with on-site clinicians, compliance, and quality stakeholders to ensure laboratory related documentation adhered to the highest level of CLIA and CAP regulatory standards.

Technical Writer

July 2014 – October 2020

Medtronic, Fridley, MN

Originated and designed clear, concise instructional materials for the safe and proper use of lifesaving products and therapies for the nationally recognized Medtronic Restorative Therapies Group.

- Created New Product Introduction (NPI) programmer app labeling as lead technical writer for clinician and patient software platforms for Pelvic Health InterStim therapy; a breakthrough smartphone commercial-off-the-shelf application that allows for enhanced clinician programming capabilities and discreet patient use of a Medtronic device.
- Mentored and lead technical writing team members through internal initiatives to enhance current processes and practice efficiencies.
- Lead design phase reviews for labeling product deliverables and generate labeling according to intended use of product.
- Developed labeling product requirements to drive robust and comprehensive labeling for target audiences.
- Strictly adhered to federal, international regulations and industry labeling standards driven by FDA and TUV regulatory bodies

Page | 4

- Lead project meetings to convey labeling development status, inter-dependencies, production issues, and timeline impacts.
- Initiated and implemented department objectives to standardize ISO symbol use for product labeling.

Technical Writer

September 2011 to July 2014

Digi International, Minnetonka, MN

Shifted career toward a passion for communication, bringing clarity and accuracy to creating technical documents and manuals, explaining complex information in a clear and concise manner, and working with scientific staff to ensure accuracy of product descriptions.

- Self-education on HTML/CSS programming; translated pdf manuals into new, interactive HTML content.
- Generated XML/HTML-based web content for XBee cellular modems
- Built Quick Start guides for Connectcore gateway.

Certified Nursing Assistant

June 2008 to January 2011

Mercy Hospital, Coon Rapids, MN

Honored to provide intimate, hands-on healthcare to patients in psychiatric, intensive care, women & children's, cardiac catheter laboratory, surgical, and cardiac units.

- Established rapport and trust with patients and staff.
- Held responsibility for monitoring vital signs, administering tests and medication, patient test and equipment preparation, charting patient records, and assisting nursing staff.

Personal Care Attendant

May 2006 to June 2008

Relieve Care, Inc., Coon Rapids, MN

Compassionately served as a lifeline for adults with a variety of mental illnesses, helping them complete basic daily routines and develop a deeper sense of independence and quality of life.

- Ensured client health through meal preparation and food intake monitoring.
- Accurately administered client's daily medications
- Coordinated community involvement activities.

Education

Master of Arts in Health and Human Services Administration

St. Mary's University, Twin Cities, MN

Bachelor of Science in Science and Technical Communication

University of Minnesota – Twin Cities, MN

Page | 5

Certified Nursing Assistant

Nursing Assistant/Home Health Aide Certification, Brooklyn Park, MN Hennepin Technical College